I love you. Oh, thank you. Be a damn shame if someone got you next, wouldn't it?
I will pray for your family that they will reap what you sow.
These are the people who are saying you shouldn't be harmed for your opinion.
I hope to see you on the street. It's your awakening slug. I expect nothing more from
this body of individuals, but I want to share with you all so that you can see what it's like
being someone who is a speaker of truth. I hope you next laughing emoji. Can't wait to see the
video of this woman's dome opened up from a slug. Don't come out in public. You will be confronted
by good people that will call you out. We will not shoot you. We will pray for you because Satan
truly has you in his grip. May the force be with you. Your days are numbered. You're going to die,
B.I. They sit down and they write this and they send it. For what it's worth, regardless of
the individuals who are out here spreading incredibly violent rhetoric that is far more than an opinion,
but instead a call to arms for all of those who want a society that is devoid of anything other than
their version of what is pure. For all of those people who are out here doing that, I and people
who agree with me have never taken the time in our lives to sit down and write violence like this
because we know that that that is the work of someone who has no interest in actual love or peace
or Christianity. No. So when I see these types of messages sent to me, I understand what world we're
in and I understand how imperative it is that I continue to be connected to that which is true
and that which is love.